<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Bluefeeds RSS Page</title>
  <link>http://bluefeeds.cs.duke.edu/home/htdocs/desktop/bluefeedsTest.xml</link>
  <description>This is the news page for the Bluefeeds web app.</description>
  <date>3/27/13</date>
  <item>
    <title>Justices Show Reluctance for Broad Marriage Ruling</title>
    <link>http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424127887324105204578385381845234780.html</link>
    <description>WASHINGTON-Two days of arguments on same-sex marriage revealed a Supreme Court uneasy about making sweeping moves on gay rights and holding doubts about whether the cases belonged before the justices at all.</description>
	<date>3/27/13</date>	
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Mass. US Senate hopefuls face off in debate</title>
    <link>http://bostonherald.com/news_opinion/us_politics/2013/03/mass_us_senate_hopefuls_face_off_in_debate</link>
    <description>The five candidates hoping to fill the U.S. Senate seat formerly held by John Kerry clashed in the first televised debates of the campaign Wednesday, as they sparred over the federal deficit, health care, Washington gridlock and other issues.</description>
	<date>3/27/13</date>	
  </item>
</channel>
<item><title>Cat has 13 babies</title><link>madeupstuff.com</link><date>3/27/13</date><description>Wowza!</description></item><item><title>Obama makes plea for gun control</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/2013/03/28/us-usa-obama-agenda-idUSBRE92R11J20130328</link><date>3/28/13</date><description> President Barack Obama attempted on Thursday to inject fresh momentum into efforts to pass gun-control legislation, pleading with U.S.</description></item><item><title>Iran, Syria and North Korea Stall Arms Treaty</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2013/03/29/world/iran-and-north-korea-block-arms-trade-treaty.html?_r=0</link><date>3/28/13</date><description>The global attempt to establish a universal standard to regulate the sale of conventional weapons suffered a temporary setback on Thursday after Iran, Syria and North Korea opposed the draft Arms Trade Treaty, blocking the consensus needed for it to pass after years of arduous negotiations.</description></item><item><title>Former soldier charged with aiding al-Qaeda in Syria</title><link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/03/28/harroun-al-qaeda-syria-soldier/2029333/</link><date>3/28/13</date><description>A former U.S. soldier was charged Thursday with taking up arms with an al-Qaeda group in attacks against the regime of Syrian President Bashar Assad.</description></item></rss>
